<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="quad_stretch">The quadriceps are a group of four muscles that run down your thighs. Virtually every athletic activity or exercise engages your quads, so it\'s important for them to be flexible and strong. To maintain healthy quads, stretch them before and after exercise. You can also use yoga to increase the flexibility in your quads, which can make them less prone to injury.</string>
    <string name="right_side_plank_crunch">Begin in a side elbow plank with your left elbow down and your right hand behind your head. Keeping your torso stable and your waist lifted, bring your right leg up toward your shoulder to lightly tap your right elbow. Lengthen your right leg back to the starting position to complete one rep</string>
    <string name="shoulder_circle">Stand tall with your arms hanging at both sides.Lift your shoulders up and roll them back in a large circular motion.</string>
    <string name="shoulder_push_up">Start in a standard pushup position with your hands slightly wider than shoulder-width apart and elbows completely locked out. Shoot your hips towards the ceiling and plant your toes into the ground so your body looks like an upside-down \'V. \' Slowly lower the top of your head towards the ground.</string>
    <string name="straight_armp">Start on all fours with wrists directly under shoulders, toes on the floor. Then, step one foot back and then the other as you engage abs and straigthen legs. Press the floor away from you with hands. You should form a straight line from shoulders to heels. Hold for 30 to 60 seconds</string>
    <string name="wall_exercise">Stand on left leg with back to wall about 3 feet away, ball of right foot pressed into wall, hands together at chest. Bend left knee and lower into a lunge (as shown). Return to start for 1 rep. Do 20 reps. Switch sides; repeat</string>
    <string name="push_up">If your maximum is under 50 pushups, do 200 a day. If your maximum is above 75, do 300 pushups a day. Repeat the ODD/EVEN routine for a total of 10 days. Then take three days off and do NO upper body pushing exercises that work the chest, triceps, and shoulders</string>

</resources>